CURRICULUM VITAE

Hyebin Seo

E-mail (Personal): seohyebin91@gmail.com

BIOGRAPHY

Hyebin Seo is currently pursuing research master's degree in English Education at Seoul National University. Her broad research interests encompass the psycholinguistics of reading and writing, methodologies in second language acquisition, technology for language teaching/learning, and doctoral education. She holds a TESOL certificate from both Yonsei University and University of California, Long Beach after undergoing 180 hours of face-to-face training. As a tutor who teaches students, she currently listens to voices and questions from the field to guide her next research question.

QUALIFICATIONS

Research Master's in English Education (Specialization in Teaching Methodology)	Seoul National University	Current
Bachelor's in English Language and Literature	Yonsei University	2024/02
TESOL Certification	Yonsei University, University of California, Long Beach	2023/06

AWARDS AND HONORS

Yonsei College of Liberal Arts Academic Conference

2023

- 1st place out of 7 teams
- Received \$300 prize
- Awarded for sentiment analysis and cultural reading of word 'mask' in Korean and US news articles.

WORK EXPERIENCE

English Tutor 2022-Current

- Lead speaking classes on daily English usage
- Ensured opportunities to practice via interesting content and activities
- Discussed pedagogy with students each week

CODING EXPERIENCE

Coding Languages

Python	2022-present
LaTeX	2023-present

LANGUAGES

Korean	C2
English	C2
German	A2